you
There was a time of doubt and fear When the path
ahead was never clear A broken boy in a world of
grey Just trying to find a brighter day Then you
appeared, a sudden light And chased away the
endless night You built a world of trust for me
For all the world to finally see You are my
guiding star, my northern light Making all my
darkest days so bright A sister's strength, a
sister's grace, a best friend's warm and kind
embrace. You are my guiding star, the truth I
know. The safest harbour, the seeds that grow.
They only see the chair I'm in They don't know
where to even begin They do not see the boy inside
The one who has no need to hide But you three see
the real me there A treasured soul beyond
compare You are the voice when I can't speak The
very strength I always seek You are my guiding
stars, my northern light Making all my darkest
days so bright
A sister's strength, a sister's grace, a best
friend's warm and kind embrace. You are my
guiding star, it's the truth I know. The safest
harbor, the seeds that grow.
Oh.
You
were my guiding star, my northern light Making
all my darkest days so bright Assistance
strength, assistance grace, a best friend's
warm and kind embrace. You are my guiding star,
it's the truth I know. The safest hop of the seeds
that grow.
This
is